EY Prysmian Marketing Intelligence Hub — an AI-powered platform for cable industry intelligence.
Secure sign-in. Phase one integrates Azure Entra ID for single sign-on.
Admin dashboard — cross-functional view of all business units.
View-as selector — preview the dashboard as any business unit.
Mining lens — copper price, active pipeline, cable demand.
Automotive lens — EV charging, EU AFIR corridors, OEM HV harness.
Alerts inbox — KPI breaches, news triggers, competitor signals.
Alert subscriptions — push to Microsoft Teams, Slack, email or in-app.
Review Queue — AI-drafted items awaiting human validation.
Accept · Edit · Reject — with structured feedback to improve the agent.
Agents page — performance metrics and feedback score per agent.
BU-scoped dashboard for an I and C user — 60-day playbook included.
Country ID — Italy. AI insight on share of wallet and white space.
Four quadrants — sales, products, competitors, share-of-wallet killer view.
Drill-down — Salesforce-style account record with opportunities and contacts.
Business Unit ID — symmetric view with country as filter.
Market Trends — Cable Demand Nowcast composite index.
Base, Up, Down scenarios — and the policy & incentive impact tracker.
Projects pipeline — 6 KPIs including green share and hyperscaler exposure.
News & Reports BU-specific feeds and specialized industry sources. AI-powered, evidence-backed, BU-aware.