Welcome to the e y Prismean marketing
intelligence hub, an always on AI
platform that turns external signals into
commercial action across Prismean's
business units.
After signing in, administrators land on
the cross functional dashboard. They see
today's I brief four key performance
indicators, flagged projects, and active
alerts.
Admins can preview the dashboard as a
business unit user would see it. The same
hero brief and metrics were flow based on
the selected BU.
For mining, the dashboard highlights
copper at the London Metal Exchange, the
active project pipeline, and estimated
cable demand across the global pipeline.
For automotive, the Focus shifts to EU
charging point growth at FIR high power
corridor tenders and original equipment
manufacturer high voltage harness
positioning.
The alerts inbox aggregates every signal
that AI agents raise, API threshold
breaches, high relevance news, project
pipeline updates, and competitor moves,
each tagged with severity, country, and
confidence score.
Each user configure subscriptions by
topic, country, and business unit and
chooses where alerts get delivered,
Microsoft Teams, Slack, email, or the in
app inbox. The platform integrates
natively with corporate collaboration
tools.
The review queue is the human in the
loop every, iDraft. Alerts, news
summaries, project records is staged here
before it reaches the wider organization.
Drafts validated, rejected, and published
are tracked separately.
The reviewer can accept, edit, or reject
each item. A feedback box captures the
reasoning which trains the agent to do
better next time. Validated items are
published to Teams or the in app feed
with one click.
The agents page exposes the performance
of every, iAgent. Last run, items
produced, feedback score, and confidence
operators see exactly how the agents are
learning from human input.
Signed in as an industrial and
construction user, the dashboard is fully
scoped to that BU, including a watch list
of segments and three recommended actions
for the next sixty days.
Country ID drills into Italy. The AI
Insight surfaces share of wallet, total
tracked market, and the highest gap
customer worth prioritizing for sales
expansion.
Four quadrants compose the country view,
sales by customer, sales by product,
competitors with momentum, and a share of
wallet view sorted by white space gap.
Clicking any row opens a Salesforce style
account record, open opportunities,
contacts tier, and Prismean relationship
details, all evidence facts.
The business unit ID view is the mirror
of country ID. The BU becomes the master,
and country becomes the filter applying
the same share of wallet lens across all
BS.
Market trends opens with the cable
demand, NOCAST. Composite index that
fuses construction PMI permits and output
to project demand climate three to six
months ahead.
Macro scenario planning projects six
months under base, up and down cases
while the policy and incentive impact
tracker maps EU programs like PNRR in
France twenty thirty onto prism in
segments.
The project's pipeline analytics show six
derived KPs. Total capacity, average
dollar per megawatt project duration,
green tax share, hyperscaler exposure,
and top investor concentration.
And finally, news and reports. Each
business unit gets its own curated feed
and a directory of canonical industry
sources. The YPrismian marketing
intelligence hub, AI powered, evidence
backed, and tailored to every business
unit. Thank you.